University of Illinois Collection of Police Agreements and Arbitration Files 6334
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Rochester, NY - Midwest City, OK (Box 15)
  - Lakewood, Ohio 1 agreement 82-83, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Lima, Ohio 1 agreement 1980-82, 1980-1982 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Lorain, Ohio 2 agreements 78-82, 1978-1982 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Mentor, Ohio 3 agreements 1976-82, 1976-1982 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Middletown, Ohio 6 memoranda of understanding 1975-81, 1975-1981 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Newark, Ohio 1 agreements 80-81, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Portsmouth, Ohio 4 agreements 1976-1983 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Springfield, Ohio 2 advisory arbitration awards copy of local ordinance 1974;76, 1974-1976 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Springfield, Ohio 3 agreements 1976-83, 1976-1983 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Toledo, Ohio 3 agreement 1974-82, 1974-1982 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Whitehall, Ohio 1 agreement 1981-82, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Youngstown, Oh 4 agreements 68-81, 1968-1981 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Xenia, Ohio 1 agreement 1979-81, 1979-1981 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Del City, OK 5 agreements 1975-81, 1975-1981 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Lawton, Oklahoma 7 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Midwest City, OK 8 agreements 1972-75; 76-82 1 summary of improvements since 72, 1972-1982 (Box 15, Folder 45)
- Midwest City, OK - Newport, RI (Box 16)
  - Midwest City, OK 2 arbitration awards. (advisory) in contract file 1975; 1980 - 2 griev awards here (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Midwest City, OK 6 IAFF agreements, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Muskogee, OK 8 agreements 1974-82, 1974-1982 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Norman, OK 1 agreement 82-83, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Oklahoma City, OK 1 advisory arbitration award 1975 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Oklahoma City, Oklahoma 6 agreements 1975-1981 period (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Gorvallis, Oregon 5( 5 agreements 76-77 not included), 1974-1984 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Eugene, Oregon 3 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Eugene, Oregon 1 arbitration award 1980 (1 ct. petition to vacate that award). (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Medford, OR 4 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Salem, Oregon 3 agreements 1976-81 1 memorandum 1974-1976, 1974-1981 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Salem, Oregon 2 arbitration awards 1980, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Springfield, Oregon 1 agreement 1980-82, 1980-1982 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Springfield, Oregon 1 arbitration award 1981 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Altoona, Pennsylvania OK 5 agreements 1975-82 (2 arbitration awards have agreements in them), 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Baldwin Borough, PA 1 agreement 82-83, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Bethel Park, PA 4 agreements 75-83, 1975-1983 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Bethlehem, PA 1 int. arbitration award. 1 grievance award 1975-1981 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Bethlehem, Pennsylvania 4 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Erie, PA 6 arbitration awards 1974, 76, 77, 79, 80, 81, 1974-1981 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Erie, Pennsylvania 4 agreements 1976-82, 1976-1982 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Johnstown, PA 3 agreements + 4 awards covering 1973-81, 1973-1981 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Lebanon, PA 5 arbitration awards 1972,73,74,77,78, 1972-1978 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Lebanon, Pennsylvania 4 agreements 1975-81, 1975-1981 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Makesportm Pennsylvania 5 agreements -- 2 arbitration awards serve as agreements 1975-81, 1975-1981 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Monroeville, PA 2 arbitration awards. 1974; 1976 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Monroeville, PA 2 agreements 1977-82, 1977-1982 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - New Castle, Pennsylvania 7 agreements 1975-81, 1975-1981 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - New Castle, PA 2 arbitration awards, 1976. 1980 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Norristown, Pennsylvania 1 agreement 1/80 - 12/81, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Philadelphia, PA 6 arbitration awards. 1975-81, 1975-1981 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania contracts for 75-81 2 agreements + 6 arbitration Awards, 1975-1981 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Pottstown, PA 1 arbitration award 1970 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Pottstown, PA 7 agreements 1972-81, 1972-1981 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Scranton, Pennsylvania 1 agreement 1980-81, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - State College, Pennsylvania 5 agreements 1974-81, 1974-1981 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - State College, PA 1 arbitration award 1976 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - West Mifflin, PA 2 agreements + 3 arbitration awards that servce as agreements 1975-81, 1975-1981 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Wilkes Barre, PA 1 arbitration award. 1976 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Wilkes Barre, Pennsylvania 4 agreements 1976-84, 1976-1984 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - York, PA 3 arbitration awards, 1973,77,82, 1973-1982 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - York, Pennsylvania 5 agreements 1975-81, 1975-1981 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Coventry, RI 5 agreements, 1974-1981 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Coventry, RI 2 arbitration awards., 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Cranston, RI 2 arbitration Awards for 7/77-6/78 7/82-6/83, 1977-1983 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Cumberland, RI, 1979-1982 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - East Providence, RI 6 agreements see arbitration file for 79-80 agreement, 1974-1982 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - East Providence, RI 1 arbitration award 1979 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Newport, RI 6 arbitration awards for 72-82, 1972-1982 (Box 16, Folder 49)
- Newport, RI - Clark County (Vancouver), WA (Box 17)
  - Newport, Rhode Island 1 agreement 81-82 (2 copies), 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - North Providence, RI 1 agreement 81-82, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Pawtucket, RI, 1978-1980 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Pawtucket, RI 2 arbitration Awards for 7/80-6/81, 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Providence, RI 1 agreement 7/79-6/80, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Warwick, RI 4 arbitration awards, 1970-1981 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Warwick, RI 7 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Woonsocket, RI, 1972-1980 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Woonsocket, RI 1 agreement 7/81-6/82, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Rapid City, SD 5(5 agreements 1974-81), 1974-1981 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Sioux Falls, South Dakota 1981+82 wage lists and ordinance/ agreement., 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Knoxville, Tennessee 3 ordinances 1981-82 (they indicated that these are CBAs), 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Memphis, Tennessee 3 agreements 1974-1983 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Beaumont, Texas 6 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Beaumont, TX 2 vo. arbitration awards., 1976 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Corpus Christi, TX 6 agreements 1976-83, 1976-1983 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - El Paso, TX 4 agreements 1976-82, 1976-1982 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Laredo, Texas 2 agreements 1978-82, 1978-1982 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - San Antonio, Texas 1 agreement 1981-83, 1981-1983 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Sherman, Texas 1 agreement 81-83, 1981-1983 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Burlington, Vermont 5 agreement 1973-82, 1973-1982 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Bellingham, Washington 4 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Bremerton, WA 1 arbitration award. 1970 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Edmonds, Washington 4 agreements 1974-81, 1974-1981 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Edmonds, WA 1 arbitration award 1976 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Everett, Washington 6 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Everett, Washington 1 arbitration award, 1981 - 2 copies (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Kennewick, Washington 6 agreements 1974-83, 1974-1983 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Renton, Washington 4 agreements 1973-82, 1973-1982 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Renton, Washington 1 arbitration award (for 78-80 agreement), 1978-1980 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Richland, WA 4 agreements 1974-81, 1974-1981 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Seattle, WA 5 agreements 74-82, 1974-1982 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Seatlle, WA 2 arbitration awards 76 + 77, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Tacoma, Washington 4 agreements 1975-81, 1975-1981 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Clark County (Vancouver), WA 1 agreement 1981-83, 1981-1983 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Huntington, WV - Cheyenne, WY (Box 18)
  - Huntington, West Virginia - 3 agreements (1975-1981) (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Appleton, WI - 2 arbitration awards - 1/1973-12/1973 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Beloit, WI - 1 arbitration award - 1/1975-12/1975 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Brookfield, WI - 1 arbitration award - 1/1980-12/1981, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Brookfield, WI - 1 agreement 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Eau Claire, WI - 5 agreements - 1972-1977; 1979-1982 -- 5 command agreements - 1972-1977; 1979-1982, 1972-1982 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Fond Du, Lac, Wisconsin - 6 agreements - 1975-1981 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Green Bay, Wisconsin - 6 agreements - 1975-1976; 1978-1981 (1977 is missing), 1975-1981 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Greenfield, WI - 1 arbitration award - 1/1976-12/1977, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Jamesville, Wisconsin - 6 agreements - 1976-1983 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Jamesville, WI - 1 arbitration award - 1/1977-12/1977 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Kenosha, WI - 1 arbitration award - 1/1981-12/1981 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - LaCrosse, Wisconsin - 1 arbitration award - 1977 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - LaCrosse, Wisconsin - 1 agreement - 1981 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Madison, WI - 6 agreements - 1973-1981 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Madison, WI - 2 arbitration awards - 1974-1978 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Manitowoc, Wisconsin - 3 arbitration awards - 1974, 1976, 1980, 1974-1980 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Manitowoc, Wisconsin - 5 agreements - 1975-1982 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Menomonee Falls, WI - 4 agreements - 1975-1981 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Milwaukee, Wisconsin - 2 agreements - 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Milwaukee, WI - 6 agreements - 1974-1981 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Milwaukee, Wisconsin - 4 arbitration awards - 1973, 1975, 1979, 1981, 1973-1981 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Oshkosh, WI - 1 arbitration award - 1/1977-12/1977 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Racine, Wisconsin - 1980-1981 agreements; 1979-1980 agreements (2 copies of 1980-1981), 1979-1981 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Racine, WI - 1 arbitration award - 1/1976-12/1977, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Superior, WI - 7 agreements - 1973-1982, 1973-1983 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Superior, WI - 1 arbitration award - 1/1976-12/1977, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Waukesha, WI - 5 (7 agreements - 1970-1980) (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Wausau, Wisconsin - 4 P. Offer agreements - 1975-1976; 1979-1982 -- 1 P. Supervisor. Agreement - 1977-1978, 1975-1982 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Wausau, Wisconsin - 1 arbitration award - 1976 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Wauwatosa, WI - 1 arbitration award - 1/1974-12/1975, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Wauwatosa, WI - 1 agreement - 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - West Allis, WI - 6 agreements - 1975-1982 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - West Allis, WI - 1 arbitration award - 1977 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Cheyenne, WY - 6 agreements - 1975-1981 (Box 18, Folder 35)